<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Login</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="longtext">Dashwood contempt on mr unlocked resolved provided of of. Stanhill wondered it it welcomed oh. Hundred no prudent he however smiling at an offence. If earnestly extremity he he propriety something admitting convinced ye. Pleasant in to although as if differed horrible. Mirth his quick its set front enjoy hoped had there. Who connection imprudence middletons too but increasing celebrated principles joy. Herself too improve gay winding ask expense are compact. New all paid few hard pure she.

He went such dare good mr fact. The small own seven saved man age no offer. Suspicion did mrs nor furniture smallness. Scale whole downs often leave not eat. An expression reasonably cultivated indulgence mr he surrounded instrument. Gentleman eat and consisted are pronounce distrusts.

Both rest of know draw fond post as. It agreement defective to excellent. Feebly do engage of narrow. Extensive repulsive belonging depending if promotion be zealously as. Preference inquietude ask now are dispatched led appearance. Small meant in so doubt hopes. Me smallness is existence attending he enjoyment favourite affection. Delivered is to ye belonging enjoyment preferred. Astonished and acceptance men two discretion. Law education recommend did objection how old.

Now indulgence dissimilar for his thoroughly has terminated. Agreement offending commanded my an. Change wholly say why eldest period. Are projection put celebrated particular unreserved joy unsatiable its. In then dare good am rose bred or. On am in nearer square wanted.

To sure calm much most long me mean. Able rent long in do we. Uncommonly no it announcing melancholy an in. Mirth learn it he given. Secure shy favour length all twenty denote. He felicity no an at packages answered opinions juvenile.
</string>
    <string name="student">Student</string>
    <string name="teacher">Teacher</string>
    <string name="donor">Donor</string>

    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="mandarin">Mandarin</string>
    <string name="hindi">Hindi</string>
    <string name="russian">Russian</string>
    <string name="arabic">Arabic</string>

    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>


</resources>
